ritholtz.com 2006-12-19

# Ritholtz Research - Privacy Policy

Ritholtz Research Privacy Policy

Overview  
Effective: 01 March 2006

This document discloses the privacy practices for Ritholtz Research.  

Ritholtz Research is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. Indeed, protection of your submitted information is key to our integrity. 

Ritholtz Research maintains this web site to provide information about its purpose and intent, as well as its use for unwarranteed guidance concerning the financial markets. We are committed to ensuring your privacy while you visit the site. The Ritholtz Research website also connects you to other sites that may offer opinions about the financial and other markets.

This privacy statement only covers the main Ritholtz Research website, not sites that may be linked to or referenced in this site. Each organization may have a different privacy statement, so you should review the privacy statement each time you submit personal information on a web site.

When you visit this web site, our web server automatically collects a limited amount of standard information essential to the operation and evaluation of the site's functions. This information includes:

  * the page from which you arrived, 

  * the date and time of your page request, 

  * the IP address your computer is using to receive information, 

  * the type and version of your browser, and 

  * the name and size of the file you request.

This information helps us assess our information services and is used only for this purpose. This information is not used to identify individuals who come to the web site. None of this information is disclosed to other public bodies or individuals.

The only information collected that is used to identify you is information you give voluntarily.

When you subscribe to our newsletter, or if you submit a question or comment, you may be asked for your name, e- mail address, or other information. This information is only used to process and respond to your question or comment, or to provide subscription or other services. This information is not disclosed except to authorized personnel who need it to maintain your subscription or answer your question or comments.

The personal information you submit is secure once it reaches our server. In transit between your computer and the server, however, it may not be secure. If you would prefer to raise a comment or question in person, please call the Ritholtz Research offices at (212) 551-1765.

Cookies  
This web site uses cookies so you can customize your online experience. Cookies are small text files that web pages place in your computer to assist you when you return to the page. If you wish, you may change the settings on your web browser to deny cookies or to warn you when cookies will be deposited.

Security  
Ritholtz Research servers use software to monitor unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, download protected files in an unauthorized way, or damage the service we provide. No attempt is made to identify users or their usage patterns except during law enforcement investigations.

More information  
For more information about any of the policies described above, please contact:  
Ritholtz.com Inquiries  
Ritholtz Research  
230 Park Avenue, Suite 1010  
New York, NY 10169

Telephone: (212) 551-1765  
E-mail:  [offices@ritholtz.com](mailto:offices@ritholtz.com)
